{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "What is the name of JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure Part 5?",
      "correct_answer": "Vento Aureo",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Vento Oreo",
        "Vanto Aureo",
        "Vento Eureo"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "What name is the main character Chihiro given in the 2001 movie &quot;Spirited Away&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Sen (Thousand)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hyaku (Hundred)",
        "Ichiman (Ten thousand)",
        "Juu (Ten)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Which part from the JoJo&#039;s Bizarre Adventure manga is about a horse race across America?",
      "correct_answer": "Part 7: Steel Ball Run",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Part 6: Stone Ocean",
        "Part 3: Stardust Crusaders",
        "Part 5: Golden Wind"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In the anime &quot;My Hero Academia&quot;, which character is shown with the ability to manipulate gravity?",
      "correct_answer": "Uraraka",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bakugo",
        "Deku",
        "Asui "
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "What caused the titular mascot of Yo-Kai Watch, Jibanyan, to become a yokai?",
      "correct_answer": "Being run over by a truck",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ate one too many chocobars",
        "Through a magical ritual",
        "When he put on the harmaki"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "Satella in &quot;Re:Zero&quot; is the witch of what?",
      "correct_answer": "Envy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pride",
        "Sloth",
        "Wrath"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In Ms. Kobayashi&#039;s Dragon Maid, who is Kobayashi&#039;s maid?",
      "correct_answer": "Tohru",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Lucoa",
        "Kanna",
        "Elma"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In the anime Black Butler, who is betrothed to be married to Ciel Phantomhive?",
      "correct_answer": "Elizabeth Midford",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rachel Phantomhive",
        "Alexis Leon Midford",
        "Angelina Dalles"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "What color is RyÅ«ko Matoi&#039;s half of the Scissor Blade in the anime Kill la KIll?",
      "correct_answer": "Red",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Green",
        "Blue",
        "Purple"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
      "question": "In &quot;Fairy Tail&quot;, what is the nickname of Natsu Dragneel?",
      "correct_answer": "The Salamander",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Dragon Slayer",
        "The Dragon",
        "The Demon"
      ]
    }
  ]
}